

**Ivana** Ristevska

**DATE OF BIRTH:** 28/11/1987

#### CONTACT

**Gender:** Female







# **ABOUT ME**

Master of Business law who never found her way in the courts, but stayed on the judgmental site in a totally different field. Highly motivated Human Resources Professional - Head Hunter, with over three years of experience in recruiting people in an IT company. Creator of the whole HR department from scratch and recruitment cycle self-composer.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

13/02/2017 - CURRENT - Skopje, North Macedonia

HR

CAPcargo

- HR department basics daily conversations with management board, company human capital needs, time management and priorities strategy, long-term strategy for acquisition of the best talents in the IT market, creation of yearly evaluation form - yearly talks and reviews, creation of employment documentation align with domestic legislation.
- Guiding the whole recruitment cycle, end-to end process
- Improvements in social relations and working atmosphere in the office.
- Head Hunting qualified professionals for all vacancies (ongoing strategy)
- Developed and implemented company policies and codes that supported long-term and short-term goals.
- Creation of the needed documentation for all new hires, and continued to build files in accordance with HR protocol.
- Assisted in maintaining all hard copy files for the HR department.
- Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner

/ Skopje, North Macedonia

# 01/07/2020 - 31/12/2020 - Berlin, Germany

## Talent Acquisition Partner - Freelance

SalesMaster Network

- Responsible for recruiting candidates located in Germany
- Responsible for whole recruitment cycle / end-to-end process
- Sourcing for new suitable candidates ( Account Manager/ Account Executive/ Sales Executive)

## 01/07/2016 - 31/12/2016

## **Client Advisor**

ProCredit Bank

- Daily banking tasks
- Acquisition new clients

/ Skopje, North Macedonia

#### 01/04/2012 - 01/03/2013

## Law Internship

Lawyer office "Oliver Ilievski"

- Responsibilities in the field of law
- Creating contracts, preparing complains and appeals
- Attending on trials in the Macedonian basic and appeal court
- Direct part from the judicial process

/ Bitola, North Macedonia

# Law Internship

Lawyer office " Aleksandar Tancevski -Gjus"

- Creating of contracts, preparing complains and appeals
- Attending on trials in the Macedonian basic and appeal court

/ Bitola, North Macedonia

# **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

**01/11/2015 - 17/07/2016** - Sofia, Bulgaria

# International Banking Program

"Young Bankers Program" ProCredit Bank

#### Skills

- improvement of communication skills
- research and presentation
- debates on variety of topics Eco-friendly working environment and social responsible company

#### Tests:

- Math
- Financial Math
- Accounting

#### 01/04/2013 - 14/09/2016 - Schmalkalden, Germany

#### Master Studies " Business Law "

"University of applied sciences - Schmalkalden"

- Master Thesis: " Human Resources Managment impact on the financial sector"- ProCredit bank case
- International HRM
- International law and contracts
- Intellectual property law
- International taxation and company law

## **01/10/2009 - 01/03/2011** - Skopje, North Macedonia

# Master studies " International Law and international relations"

Ss." Cyril and Methody"Univeristy , Faculty of Law " Justinijanus Primus"

- Master thesis- 2012 year topic "European regulations of investment funds in European Union"
- International private and public law
- International political relations
- Human rights, Institutions of EU, Mediator/ Arbiter law

## 01/10/2006 - 01/05/2009 - Skopje, North Macedonia

## Bachelor Law studies

Ss."Cyril and Methody" University, Faculty of Law "Justinijanus Primus"

- Statutory law, sociology of law, history of law
- Political systems, economy (micro and macro), finance law

# LANGUAGE SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): Macedonian

**OTHER LANGUAGE(S):** 

**English** 

<b>Listening</b> C1	<b>Reading</b> C1	Spoken production C1	Spoken interaction C1	<b>Writing</b> C1
German Listening B2	<b>Reading</b> B2	Spoken production B2	Spoken interaction B2	<b>Writing</b> B2

# **DIGITAL SKILLS**

Microsoft Office / Linkedin\ / Outlook / Social Media/Social Network

# ORGANISATIONAL SKILLS



# **Organisational skills**

- Strong interpersonal skills and positive and strong work ethic
- Communication and motivation
- Forward planning and strategic thinking
- Self-motivated, hard-working individual
- Ability to work independently in a fast-paced environment